http://www.klhindustries.com/website-terms-use

KLH Industries Inc.
Search this site:
Home Website Terms of Use
Please read the website terms of use carefully before using the KLH Industries, Inc. (“KLH”). By accessing and using this Site, you agree to each of the terms and conditions set forth herein ("Terms of Use"). Additional terms and conditions applicable to specific areas of this Site or to particular content or transactions are also posted in particular areas of the Site and, together with these Terms of Use, govern your use of those areas, content or transactions. These Terms of Use, together with applicable additional terms and conditions, are referred to as this "Agreement".
KLH reserves the right to modify this Agreement at any time without giving you prior notice. Your use of the Site following any such modification constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Agreement as modified. The last date these Terms of Use were last revised is set forth below.
Use Of Site
Copyright
Trademarks
Privacy Policy
Links To Third Party Websites
Linking To This Site
Credit Card Surcharges
Downloading Files
Disclaimer Of Warranties
Limitation Of Liability
Indemnification
Use of Site
You may use the Service, the Site, and the information, writings, images and/or other works that you see, hear or otherwise experience on the Site (singly or collectively, the “Content”) solely for your non-commercial, personal purposes and/or to learn about KLH products and services. No right, title or interest in any Content is transferred to you, whether as a result of downloading such Content or otherwise. KLH reserves complete title and full intellectual property rights in all Content. Except as expressly authorized by this Agreement, you may not use, alter, copy, distribute, transmit, or derive another work from any Content obtained from the Site or the Service, except as expressly permitted by the Terms of Use.
Copyright
The Site and the Content are protected by U.S. and/or foreign copyright laws, and belong to KLH or its partners, affiliates, contributors or third parties. The copyrights in the Content are owned by KLH or other copyright owners who have authorized their use on the Site. You may download and reprint Content for non-commercial, non-public, personal use only. (If you are browsing this Site as an employee or member of any business or organization, you may download and reprint Content only for educational or other non-commercial purposes within your business or organization.
Trademarks
You are prohibited from using any of the marks or logos appearing throughout the Site without permission from the trademark owner, except as permitted by applicable law.
Privacy Policy
Click here to view KLH’s privacy policy.
Links to Third-Party Websites
Links on the Site to third party web sites or information are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Site. Such links do not constitute or imply an endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation by KLH of the third party, the third-party web site, or the information contained therein. KLH is not responsible for the availability of any such web sites. KLH is not responsible or liable for any such web site or the content thereon. If you use the links to the web sites of KLH affiliates or service providers, you will leave the Site, and will be subject to the terms of use and privacy policy applicable to those web sites.
Linking to this Site
You may link any public webpage that appears on the Site Map, in additional to all newsletter articles. You may not link to pages that do not meet the before mentioned criteria. You may not mirror or frame the home page or any other pages of this Site on any other web site or web page.
Credit Card Surcharges
KLH will impose a credit card surcharge equal to the less of: (i) the average merchant discount rate for the applicable credit card surcharged; or (ii) four percent (4%).
Downloading Files
KLH cannot and does not guarantee or warrant that files available for downloading through the Site will be free of infection by software viruses or other malicious code, program, or files.
Disclaimer of Warranties
KLH MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE SITE’S OPERATION OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT OR MATERIALS INCLUDED ON THIS SITE. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY THE LAW, KLH HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS OF ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
Limitation of Liability
KLH WILL NOT BE HELD LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOU USE THIS SITE SOLELY AT YOUR OWN RISK. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL KLH OR SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, ECONOMIC OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOSS OF DATA OR LOSS OF USE DAMAGES OR LOST PROFITS) ARISING OUT OF OR CONNECTED WITH THE SITE (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ITS OPERATION, ITS CONTENTS OR THE INFORMATION OR MATERIALS CONTAINED THEREIN, OR THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE ANY OTHER SITE LINKED TO THE SITE, OR ANY CONTENT CONTAINED IN ANY SUCH SITE, OR THESE TERMS, OR THE PRIVACY POLICY APPLICABLE TO THIS SITE) EVEN IF KLH, ITS SUPPLIERS, OR LICENSORS HAVE BEEN NOTIFIED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY DAMAGES. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU IN SUCH STATES. THE RESPECTIVE LIABILITY OF KLH, ITS SUPPLIERS AND LICENSORS SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.
Indemnification
You understand and agree that you are personally responsible for your behavior on the Site. You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless KLH, its parent companies, subsidiaries, affiliated companies, joint venturers, business partners, licensors, employees, agents, and any third-party information providers to the Service from and against all claims, losses, expenses, damages and costs (including, but not limited to, direct, incidental, consequential, exemplary and indirect damages), resulting from or arising out of your use, misuse, or inability to use the Site, the Service, or the Content, or any violation by you of this Agreement.
Miscellaneous
Suppliers
Privacy Policy
Contact
Website Terms of Use
Sitemap
Submit Online RFQ
© 2020 KLH Industries Inc.
